<!DOCTYPE ui:UiBinder SYSTEM "http://dl.google.com/gwt/DTD/xhtml.ent">
<ui:UiBinder xmlns:ui="urn:ui:com.google.gwt.uibinder" xmlns:g="urn:import:com.google.gwt.user.client.ui">
	<ui:style>
		.welcomeText{
			width:900px;
			text-align:justify;
			text-justify:inter-word;
		background-color:AntiqueWhite; 
<!-- 			background-color: #87CEFA; -->
		}

	</ui:style>
	<g:FlowPanel ui:field='homeFlowPanel' >
	<g:HTMLPanel>
<!-- 	    <g:HTMLPanel styleName='{style.welcomeText}'> -->
	<br/>
	<h2>Welcome to the Clinical Scenario Repository.</h2>  
	<!-- <p>The Clinical Scenario Repository is hosted by the <g:Anchor href="http://www.mdpnp.org/">MD PnP</g:Anchor>  Team.</p>  -->
	<p class="welcomeText">The Clinical Scenario Repository is hosted by the <a href="http://www.mdpnp.org/">MD PnP</a> Program.</p>
	
	<p class="welcomeText">A <em>clinical scenario</em> is a brief description of a clinical situation or event. The purpose of the clinical scenario is 
	to provide a background and ilustrate the need for the development of technical solutions. Solutions for these 
	scenarios will be generalizable and will create building blocks for interoperability to address many other healthcare needs.</p>

	<p class="welcomeText">The aim of this open repository of Clinical Scenarios Website is to provide a web-based user interface that will allow clinicians, clinical engineers, and other users to enter, revise, annotate, and maintain clinical scenarios, thus identifying specific clinical and technical challenges.</p>

	<h3>Benefits of registration.</h3> 
	<p class="welcomeText">Registering is easy and free. Although any visitor can view the approved scenarios without logging into the website, <em>registered users</em> are allowed enhanced functionality such as submitting a scenario for approval or exporting search results or specific scenarios. Use the "Sign in" button on the webpage to register.</p>

	<h3>Disclaimer.</h3> 
	<p class="welcomeText">The MD PnP program just hosts this website to promote a shareable data base of clinical scenarios. Users are responsible for the content they submit or retrieve from this website and the consecuences of the use of such information. No protected health information such as names of individuals or institutios is allowed in the submission of clinical scenarios.</p>
	
	<h3>Contact us.</h3> 
	<p class="welcomeText">Click 
	    <a href="mailto:md.pnp.team@gmail.com?Subject=Clincical%20Scenario%20Repository" target="_top">here</a> 
	    to contact the Clinical Scenario Repository Administrators</p>
	
	<p class="welcomeText"> © 2013 MD PnP Program</p>
	</g:HTMLPanel>
	</g:FlowPanel>
</ui:UiBinder>